HECTOR VASQUEZ

FRONT END DEVELOPER ● BOLÍVAR, VENEZUELA, BOLIVARIAN REPUBLIC OF 📞 +58 4128580282

DETAILS

Bolívar, Venezuela, Bolivarian Republic of +58 4128580282 hvasquezdev@gmail.com

• LINKS •

https://www.hectorvasquez.me/

https://github.com/Hvasquezdev

SKILLS

JavaScript

HTML & CSS

Vue.js

Vuex

Nuxt.js

Three.js

React.js

Tailwind.Css

Node.js

• LANGUAGES •

Git

Spanish; Castilian

English

· HOBBIES ·

Learn new things by reading books or blog post, play videogames and play table tennis

PROFILE

Passionate and innovative Front end developer with about 2 years of experience maintaining, building and delivering immersive and engaging user experience, mobile first, accessibility and SEO optimization through Front end web development. Proactive developer learning new things and improving current skills daily. Proeficent with the most modern technologies like JavaScript ES6 + / Vue.Js / Nuxt.js

Learning everyday is my path to be a better developer.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Frontend at Café Center Restaurant, Ciudad Bolívar

March 2017 - October 2017

Restaurant online reservation system

- · Delivered full responsive web app, cross-browser compatible and accessibility
- · Front-end with vanilla JavaScript and Google material design

Frontend at Policia Municipal, Ciudad Bolívar

April 2018 - November 2018

Traffic taxes system

- · Developed with Vue.js, Bulma.Css
- · Created accessible, optimized and full responsive mobile first web app
- · Connect Front-end with the database made in PHP and MySQL

Full-Stack at Contraloria Municipal del Estado Bolívar, Ciudad Bolívar

February 2019 — December 2019

Intranet web app to send internal messages

- Delivered single page app with responsive (Mobile first), cross-browser compatible and performance optimized
- Developed with modern technologies: Vue.js, Tailwind.Css, Node.Js, Socket.io, MySQL, Express.js

Frontend at Nextreality Digital

January 2020

Principal Front-End developer to optimize existing web pages and create new web apps

- · Optimize 3D app made with Three.js and A-frame
- · Optimize web pages to better SEO, accessibility and performance
- · Create new web apps fully responsive and cross-browser optimized
- · Fix old responsive design in the existing web pages
- · Develop new 3D features with Three.js
- · Connect web apps with an API to fetch and send data

EDUCATION

Ingeniería Informática, Intitulo Universitario de Tecnología del Estado Bolívar, Ciudad Bolívar

2015 - January 2020

COURSES

Arquitecto FrontEnd, Platzi

February 2019

Carrera de JavaScript, Platzi
January 2020
 Carrera de Vue.Js, Platzi
March 2019
 Intermediate React.js, Frontend Masters
March 2020
 JavaScript Hard Parts, Frontend Masters
April 2020
 Introducción al Desarrollo Web: HTML y CSS, Google